all right
people join up ask up one person one
person in us six people seven nine here
we go
what up crow welcome to myself driving
til your little Prius commas
self-driving Toyota Prius I didn't
really do anything
I just Cheerilee it and talk I'm the
periscope so we're actually using the
Prius is longitudinal control and this
is the comma a I lateral control oh oh
wait a second we have something we can't
show off in this car we show well hey
you know cats out know that don't worry
internal prototypes in total from tennis
yeah no I'm not
we won't even talk about it don't don't
talk about it just like yeah it's an e
oh yeah we have an e out yeah I mean our
self-driving Prius Wow can't believe I
forgot about that
yeah um we have an extra you know well
that's yeah that Prius has a computer in
it too um yeah the periscopes and we
didn't like why are the periscopes
always kind of low-quality but yeah so
we're using the longitudinal control
that's built into this car lateral
control is what we have we're actually
on our way right now to the Toyota
dealership to buy another Toyota
we love Toyota man Toyota's are great
right this turn here and we'll see what
it does
oh not what's with our fare um the Prius
has a significantly higher torque limit
than the Honda Civic
significantly higher so that's why when
I'm driving the Prius I always keep my
hands touching the wheel it's not
actually moving the wheel I'm not moving
the my god yeah
but yeah I put the speed up here get on
this Highway
doesn't that thing park by itself yeah
it does it does park by itself but it
does not drive itself
the Honda lane-keeping system is much
better than the Toyotas line keeping
system the Toyotas lean keeping systems
practically non-existent
yeah there's a lot of berry researchy
stuff going on in this car right now
yeah check out the wheel
my hands and hands are an inch from the
steering wheel sturdy
it's just ready in case it does do
anything if you've been quickly to
respond to this the release version this
probably won't be the case
oh yeah pretty well when I said we got
off of three three be a billion for each
other
ready through me look at that term
that's good
thanks genders diners on our thing yeah
ten days of thoughts
where is e where does it yesterday man
people have a lot of computer questions
genders is tech ops a comma AI it does
something of interest oh yeah right
wow this is huge props of the controls
team forgetting this to work
is it better than Tesla out of Paris
did not a miss Carnot so the Civic is
actually even better than this car this
is our latest in prototype so our plan
is by the end of the year to support
almost all the Honda's and all the
Toyota rav4 hybrid absolutely well what
year what year what year for your rav4
we're actually going to buy a rav4 right
now
20:17 absolutely absolutely it's gonna
work yeah it'll work on all someone's
asking me what the best part for this
isn't if there are any Hyundai said oh
no Hyundai's now the best car right now
is the Honda Civic our flagship by the
end of this year will be the Toyota
Prius so if you want now Civic if you
want future Prius
free stuff no no no when I wrap it today
what about Chrysler Dodge No
this is a greeting
into the wheel accident
makes the Prius the future so the Prius
does a lot of really cool sensors in it
so we have like a blind spot awareness
sensor see the mirror over there
it has an electric motor which you can
control much more precisely than a
gasoline motor it's a nice car I'm happy
with this I'm impressed with Toyota I
say the same thing about the Civic like
both of these when you compare like like
a Honda Civic
oh I went on with the GM with the GM
looking a buyer look at a buyer a bolt a
bolt
man that's that's that's that's see
that's a prototype neo yeah I mean you
couldn't even like look and see what's
on the screen it's no different from
open pilot except it's got a pink line
instead of a purple yeah maybe yeah
we'll see we got we can we have a
phenomenal new intern yeah yeah
the pink line control pink line control
is great man man when I talked about
silky smooth
that's fine so we've gone we've gone
five minutes now without a disengagement
this is coming eyes real
your turn free labor and no we pay our
interns oh absolutely better interns we
parent does really well can you apply it
more torque to the first in the Civic
yes we can
our go driving in Pittsburgh
each autonomous driving up anything
outfits book
autonomy we are - - and no one else and
no one else has anything else that isn't
- anybody who tells Balkan one exception
Howdy's traffic em assist might be level
three but the only difference between
level two three and four is liability
there's no other difference between
these levels so I'm actually gonna
disengage and engage because which it
cannot so Oh sort of no I can't no but
that's what what's nice about having the
Blind Spot Assist incentives if you got
charged for your panda it means it's on
the way it means we sent it out
absolutely
yeah you got charged for your pair that
means it shipped either yesterday or
will ship tonight yeah and us uh you
know what if you can do a close-up of
the giraffe I showed off giraffes this
morning
so these cones be mine on that I got
this long jab
I got it I gotta see the shoes I'm
driving a car oh man this is not the car
driver you guys the cars not this bad
but yeah so we're actually driving on a
panda right now which way straight
so this is actually all of the control
signals being spoken to the priest right
now are going through a panda pandas are
universal car interfaces they can be
used for shipper apps they can be used
for anything you're gonna be turning
left up at the top
so yeah if you if you bought a panda you
are getting in early yeah this is this
this panda that's running right here is
the exact same panda that we're shipping
out there's nothing special about it
wait what no you're actually following
turn left and then you're yeah you're
getting this Lane right there on our way
to melody Toyota should we live stream
the Toyota dealership oh we love Toyota
dealership I realized it people we got
66 mom oh yes they should wash off the
giraffe yeah check out so that's a
that's a panda up there yeah that's a
that's a giraffe which is how we're
connected into the Toyota we have a zoo
we have it's a whale we have giraffes
and pandas yeah we're gonna we're gonna
we're gonna make Li be koalas but koalas
were cancelled yeah yeah no one really
is time for koalas yeah yeah I'm see
also don't replace the rear view mirror
on cars anymore
we mount right to the windshield so this
neo has radar disabled and using the
Prius ACC oh so we're using the Prius
radar as well and we're using the
Priuses ACC yeah
well we're talking to the Prius trainer
is it possible to make a sound happen to
the neo and a certain effect occurs oh
we use the sounds from the car but yeah
I mean that's certainly possible
remember Neos run a OS which is just
like a slight variant to Android so yeah
it's really easy if you can make Android
class sound you can make a deal play us
out which point six miles your time
stay straight cool now unfortunately
since I'm using the Toyota ACC I have to
wait until we get to let's see if we can
make this turn here there you go guys
there you go look at that um since I'm
using the Toyota ACC I can't engage it
below 28 it also does a terrible job of
fusing with stopped cars like this is on
oh my god this you see it felt that hard
stop this is not our system that is what
our system does so much better yeah all
the steering has been our system but
we're gonna we're gonna work on getting
on getting the off so no stopping
yes stop it well Toyota low quality stop
and go yeah like look here so you can
see here like we're eight meters from
the UH from the car in front of us like
why did it stop Oh
vision only ACC not a high priority for
us a lot of these cars do have radars so
I also have to tap on the pedal to get
it to resume I see and it disengages the
cruise control if it loses the radar
track our system doesn't do this you
don't really need to
the volta loss up two to three meters on
stop and go after tree two to three is a
lot more reasonable eight is completely
unfeasible like eight meters from the
front of your car to the front of their
car
I thought Pierce at full speed DRC see
it does try to use it I would not call
it good good is not the word I used here
good is not the word I would use to
describe the nowhere
you guys who watch these periscopes you
get it on the latest and greatest stock
you say sign priority but is it viable
for open pilot users what oh oh oh
vision only as you see what car do you
have that you're really deep vision only
as you see far
you're better off just going on eBay and
buying like a Delfy radar or something
there it is melody Toyota you - you big
fan of Toyota dealership is the master
fest same thing I was right Turner
sketchy
left left - neow the right time
this vision ACC landing the video
combined with existing radar data yes
but what car do you have that you want
vision only ACC for Subarus originally
yeah I know superficially super us have
two cameras with a wide base line that
makes vision only a lot easier
my q5 doesn't have freedom but sue
by the way if you don't have radar you
can certainly still get open pilot to
work longitudinally yeah so this this
isn't you can actually just turn this
off in the in the settings the use of
the customs Canela yeah really
when they switch that's all a Bosch mor
for a while yeah I mean only ACC it
really depends on what you want to do
like if all you want to do is gas only
cruise control then the vision only ACC
and open Pilar is already good enough
for that if you want to start doing the
brake if you want to smooth braking
experience you'll have to wait for it to
get a bit better but show me that you
have a car that you can control the gas
and the brakes on if you show me that
I'll put some more engineering effort
into uh will open pilots doing work with
that radar yes absolutely yeah
the entrance I missed the entry using
the street you can go straight in around
that time my band's because I haven't
left the house in thoughts on Google and
pressing 1 billion and lift oh you guys
won't see self-park oh ho this is not
our son nervous myself Park is too bad
Georgia spiking my partner also you can
judge it to set some more fun you know
[Music]
this car has so many things that beep at
you
it's really like poorly done because
like you never know which beeps are like
important beeps this this is the car who
like you know the boy beep wolf oh it's
the P button
all right periscope yo yo
so we're out
to buy a Toyota but yeah by the end of
the year guys open pilots should support
top 10 cars sold in America the top 3
things won't buy Tesla oh I think has
will take over the auto industry in
America I think they're already worth
more than 4
um well someone buy for it I don't know
they've been a company for it's kind of
sad when you think about it
Ford's been a company for like a hundred
years and like your mustache showed up I
don't know where that was true
no but guys um so by the end of the year
open pilot we're gonna support top 10
cars sold in America at the top 3 or
pickup trucks go pick up trucks on the
top the fourth is the Camry the Camry is
going to work if you have the 2018 Camry
number 5 is the Honda Civic the Civic is
going to work if you have the Honda
sensing package then the next two I
believe are the Corolla and the rav4 and
both of those either the Corolla CRV and
the rav4 CRV is gonna be supporting the
Touring package parole in the rav4 all
of them are gonna work gas and brake on
Subaru so when you show me a video of
gas and brake on Subaru like with a
joystick and I'll work on I'll work on
organ vision for ya
well I won't work on the pitch but kabel
work on the vision you are
the new Bojack season was disappointing
just putting that out there but uh yeah
all right we're gonna buy a car
was it really disappointing the new Bo
Jackson oh yeah